Abdulhafeez Hamed Zalloom

Amman, Jordan



aboodhammed98@outlook.com



+962778133613



linkedin.com/in/abdulhafeez-hamedzalloom-996524155

Summary

Working as a Software Engineering in the Web Development industry

In the Back-End field, working with Django and DRF (Django Rest Framework), Git, and GitHub

In the Front-End field, working with (HTML, CSS, JS, JQuery, and Bootstrap)

In SDLC, working with Agile Methodology, in Scrum

always find out to have more experience and grow up in this field

Experience



Software Engineer

Sitech

Apr 2022 - Present (9 months +) Nafith Project



Full-stack Developer

Sitech

Nov 2021 - Feb 2022 (4 months)

it was so exciting to me to have learnt full stack developer by python Django in BackEnd with greatest people and teams in #sitech .. I learnt more skills I didn't have it, meet great people and learn from them ... thanks to #sitech to open this opportunity



Social Media Marketing (freelance)

A Plus Business & study center Jul 2018 - Sep 2019 (1 year 3 months)

Social media Officer

Skapere

Feb 2018 - Apr 2018 (3 months)

Education



Princess Sumaya University for Technology

Computer Science Oct 2019 - Jan 2023

Licenses & Certifications

- Introduction to Programming Using Python Python Software Foundation 5A0CEF231AFD
- Oracle Database 12c: SQL Fundamentals The Hope International
- HTML5 and CSS3 Pirple 8mtwroyo6l

Skills

GitHub • Git • Django REST Framework • Agile Methodologies • MySQL • JavaScript • Bootstrap • Python (Programming Language) • Full-Stack Development • PL/SQL